♪ California love ♪
♪ California knows how to party ♪
♪ In the city of LA ♪
♪ In the city of good ol' Watts ♪
♪ In the city, the city of Compton ♪
♪ We keep it rockin',
we keep it rockin' ♪
♪ Now let me welcome everybody
To the Wild Wild West ♪
♪ A state that's untouchable
Like Eliot Ness ♪
♪ The track hits your eardrum
Like a slug to your chest ♪
♪ Pack a vest for your Jimmy
In the city of sex ♪
♪ We in that sunshine state
Where the bomb-ass hemp be ♪
Yeah.
Who are you?
What are you doing in my room?
Where's Michael?
Ah!
Huh?
You missed!
Come on!
This old bitch.
Shit.
Works every time.
With your old ass.
When was the last time
you been to the dentist, huh?
Money.
♪ So come on and chickity-check yo' self
Before you wreck yo' self ♪
♪ Chickity-check yo' self
♪ Yeah, come on and check yo' self
Before you wreck yo' self ♪
♪ 'Cause shotgun bullets
Are bad for your health ♪
Do you know what the definition
of insanity is, Sasha?
Doing the same thing over and over
and expecting a different result.
You cling to the old ways
like a tick on a dog's ass.
And look at where that's gotten us.
You've made your point.
I accept your terms.
I think we're a little
beyond that now, don't you?
I made a mistake.
You want this? You have it.
There you go again, lacking imagination.
"You, our, yours."
These are words of division, darling.
And divided, we are vulnerable.
But together?
The sky is the limit.
And why rent when you can own?
No. No, no, no. No, no, no!
No!
We've got big plans
for the Valley, cabrón.
Maybe we can dig you up in 100 years
and show you
what we've done with the place.
No, no. Please!
No. No!
Hey, Bud. Nice look.
...everything, the package isn't here.
Bud, I need your rent.
So I'll look again...
Oh shit!
I'm calling because your
husband is late again picking up Paige.
Do you have an ETA
of when we should expect him?
All right, but this is
the third time this week that he's late.
I shouldn't have to remind you that...
Just a sec. He's pulling up.
Paige!
- Hey, Daddy!
- Come on, baby!
Well, what up?
- Who's your favorite daddy?
- You.
I'm your only daddy, I hope. What's up?
- You're late, you know?
- What?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
You know why I'm late? 'Cause this job.
- Work is dumb.
- Oh, well, yes, it is.
And what do you have in your hand? Oh...
- A little something.
- Shaboom! I love that.
How about this? Hmm?
- All right.
- Can we go to Yogurtworld?
Yogurtworld. Oh, Pickle, I don't know.
Your mom is already upset
because we're late.
Whose fault is that?
Harsh.
But true. Roll the dice.
And we gonna roll out. Here we go.
Hands in the air!
We taking off.
Yogurtworld, we're on the way.
Yogurtworld!
I'm gonna get strawberry.
There it is.
Daddy's
getting... strawberry.
Pow.
Wow. Mmm.
Boom! Got it.
- Boom!
- Yeah. Boom.
Got it.
You got it.
You're so weird.
If you only knew. All right, come on.
Excuse me, do you guys have
any Black History Month discounts?
♪ Oh, come on, come on
Come on, people now ♪
♪ Express yourself ♪
♪ Oh, come on, come on
Come on, people now ♪
Home sweet home.
Home sweet...
-We home!
You're late.
- Hey.
- Hi.
We went to Yogurtworld.
Oh! Did you?
Snitches get stitches.
We were gonna keep that between us.
Sorry.
It's all good. Gimme
five on your way up.
- Whoo!
- Nothing can stop you. All the way up.
Making a ten-year-old
a part of your lies now. Charming.
She told me that she liked hanging
out with her old man. I was like...
Oh, she wanted to hang out with you.
See, that's something she coulda done if
you'd taken her to school like I asked.
Well, I told you I had to go, and..
That pool cleaning appointment
this morning?
- Exactly.
- Right.
Whose house was it?
It was Mrs... uh... Mrs. Jones' house.
Where's she live?
She, uh...
With Mr. Jones. That's exactly...
- Right over there on Mr. Jones Way.
- Oh my God. Bud.
We'd get much further
if you'd be straight with me.
- I am being straight.
- You're not.
I am being straight, but the question is,
what is that sponge doing on the ground?
And this? What is all this?
I am fixing the broken tile.
Mm-hmm. I see that. And why?
Uh, what does it matter?
- You don't live here anymore.
- Wow, that's what we doing?
What I was gonna tell you
is that this tile goes...
Joss, what's this? This a new door?
Uh...
A door with five locks doesn't exactly
send the right impression
to potential buyers.
Buyers? Buyers?
What are you talking about, Joss?
I didn't want to tell you this way,
but...
I'm thinking about selling the house
and taking my mom up on her offer.
You and your momma.
Florida?
What are you talking about?
You can't move to Florida.
All her friends are here.
I'm here. Her world is here.
She needs stability.
She has stability.
She got you. She got me.
She got Yogurtworld.
Ain't no Yogurtworld in Florida!
Yeah, and she also has a school
that she's not gonna be able to go to
unless we pay tuition by Monday.
Then let's pay the tu... Mon..
Monday? Monday, like in seven days?
Yeah, which you would know
if you had checked your voice mails.
Is that the stability you talk about?
- How much is it?
- Five grand.
Five thousand dollars for a child?
Mm-hmm. And she needs braces.
- What's wrong?
- Her teeth are jacked up.
She always says she likes her teeth
'cause they look like my teeth.
That's my point.
Okay. Well, how much are braces?
What? Five, six hundred dollars?
- Without insurance, try six grand.
- Six grand?
But I did find a guy
who quoted me $4,800.
- I know we done been through a whole lot.
- Yeah.
Just, please,
don't take my daughter away.
Till Monday. Just give me till Monday.
Ten grand. Tuition, teeth, everything.
Okay, fine. I will give you till Monday.
Come on, hug me.
- Hug me.
- I'm hugging you.
- Stop listening to your mom. She drinks.
- What?
- Uh, Bud.
I have one more question.
Paige said that there's
a porn star living in your building?
How does she even know
what a porn star is?
It's the Valley, Joss.
They live amongst us.
♪ Still gotta pray for the LA, we play
Black folks still bring into the true ♪
♪ But I still got love
So I'm comin' through ♪
♪ With a trunk full of funk
That I make ya ♪
♪ Separate the real from the fake
Each and every.. ♪
Fellas. 'Sup, baby?
Who's thirsty? Hmm?
Business is booming, I see.
What's up, Eddie? Oh!
You always fast.
Is Troy here?
♪ So, baby, take me higher ♪
All right.
Troy!
Decided to take me up on my offer?
Not today, not tomorrow, not anytime.
- Here, you thirsty?
- Ooh. Thank you!
- Get some of that in you.
- Fifteen hundred is good money.
Like I said, Troy,
Snake Eyes ain't for sale now.
Everything's for sale.
You just have to be desperate enough.
- So, what do you got for Troy?
- Desperate, huh?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I got for Troy.
Money. All right.
Right there.
- Ooh, nice.
- Count that.
Let's see, uh...
- Oh, this is a young male.
- Mm-hmm.
Garden-variety, it's like Eastern...
Hey, smoker...
- Nasty habit, don't you think?
- Yeah.
He would have died from smoking
if he wasn't dead already.
Count the shit up.
Let's check this out.
Uh, yeah, you see there?
- Yeah, solid bloodline.
- Mm-hmm.
Must've gotten here
through Mexico or something.
- He fed recently, you see that?
- Yeah.
Okay. Well, how much?
Eight hundred? $800? A piece?
No, both.
Troy, what are you talking about?
Look at that again.
- That's worth at least four grand.
- Down at the Union.
- Why don't you try the Union?
- Come on.
I can't go to the Union. You know that.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I... I forgot you can't go to the Union.
That's why you're coming to me. Huh?
And I'm offering you 800 for both.
All right, forget it.
Just check the Elder's.
Elder?
That's a different
story. That's 20 grand.
Boom. Perfect. Done.
Yeah, yeah.
If she had been an Elder,
which she's not.
Check this out.
A decade early
and a whole lot of dollars short,
so I can give you
like two grand for this.
- Two thousand, Troy?
- Mm-hmm.
Two thousand?
Listen, I don't think you understand.
I need cash today.
Then go and rob a bank or do something.
I'm a businessman!
Forget the Elder's.
How about this? Silver.
Hmm?
Silver? This is...
- Just gonna put that in your mouth, huh?
- This plated shit? Please, Bud.
You wanna make a deal or not?
Shit.
Snake Eyes, 1,500.
Ah, twelve.
You said 1,500 when I walked in here.
It is 1,500.
Before I knew you were desperate.
That's everything I have.
Well, I think you have something else.
Are those Jordans?
What size?
Hey. Hey, Pickle. How you doing?
Dad, are we moving?
- Are we what?
- Are we moving?
No. No. What makes you think that?
Mom says I might have
to start a new school.
That's what Mom says, huh?
Well, you know Mom is a jokester,
and I love her to death, but...
But we're not going anywhere.
You're not going anywhere, okay?
Okay, good. Thanks, Daddy.
- I love you.
- I love you too!
I need you, bro.
We have already agreed
to take delivery of the product
and to help with
placement in Simi Valley.
You had no authority to take out Sasha.
I'm going to have to rethink our deal.
Sasha is the past,
and I am the future.
We already own the night,
but my product
will allow us to seize the day.
So here is your choice.
You join me, and we take over the
Valley, or you can join him. Comprendes?
My precious...
It's just one man.
I can still smell him.
Find him.
♪ I may be a fool with my money
But don't call me broke ♪
♪ I may act funny on occasions
But I ain't no joke ♪
♪ I can drink a bottle of whiskey down
And start a fight or two ♪
♪ I ain't George Foreman or Ali
But I've won a few ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ I'm a truck-driving
Harley-riding son of a gun ♪
♪ Loud country music bumping
Come and have you some fun ♪
♪ Deer-hunting, beer-guzzling
Boot-wearin', Southern man ♪
♪ And I don't give a damn ♪
Big J, you ain't changed a bit, baby.
I see you. What's happening?
You know me,
cutting necks and cashing checks.
Yeah. Thanks for meeting me, man.
Least I can do for the player that
snatched my ass out the sandbox twice.
How's Seeger?
Same.
- Or worse.
- Damn.
You think he'll listen?
- Things have changed since you left.
- I ain't never left, Big J.
Well, since you got
your ass kicked out the Union.
Look here. I'm putting my name and
my ass on the line by vouching for you.
Can you play this shit by the books?
I got to. I got to get that Union card,
or I'm gonna lose my family.
Look, I need ten large
in the next five days,
or Joss is gonna take Paige
down to Florida.
That's bad.
The Union is the only place
gonna give me that kind of coin.
- I got you. Lock and load.
- All right.
She's done this before, man.
Pump faking, whatever.
But right now, it seems like it's real.
Hi, Momoko!
How are you?
Momoko.
Yes?
Pink penguin puffy pants.
See you ain't missed a step,
Big J.
JJ Perry to the trade counter.
- Wow.
- JJ Perry to the trade counter.
I don't know
how I feel about this.
Things really done changed
around here, huh?
Yeah, we ain't just 818 no more.
We done went international.
Look, Paris even blowing up tonight.
Hmm.
Bet money's good out there.
Let's go and get this thing over with.
How's the shirt look?
Stop being nervous, man.
Pull yourself together.
Hey, Big John.
Well, hello, sunshine.
He's expecting you,
but he's in one of his moods today.
I took this meeting
out of respect for you, Big John.
God knows I wouldn't be
sitting here without your support.
But, uh, I'm certain we all remember
that Mr. Jablonski's previous tenure
as a Union member was...
chock-full of incidents.
Let's just take a look.
Northridge, 2014, violated code 103.
Encino, 2015, fleshed out a nest
while a child's birthday party
was unfolding next door,
endangering civilians,
violating codes 921, 833, and 605,
the worst of which was the failure
to notify law enforcement in due time.
- That was a good bust. What happened was..
- And to top it all off...
Canoga Park, 2017,
violated code 101, endangering
a fellow Union member's life.
Critical injury sustained.
He already had g... gout. He had gout.
Each of these incidents...
meriting a lifelong suspension.
And yet, time and again,
you were given warnings.
Why should I extend you
yet another lifeline?
Ralph, let me be the first to tell you.
- Bud here, he's a new man.
- Yeah.
Is that right?
Yes, sir. Absolutely. I'm a changed man.
I've cut out, uh...
pork and cartoons and
minimal white women.
Bud, I'm curious. Uh...
If you were in my position,
sitting across
from a man such as yourself,
would you let you back in?
If that person
that is in question admits fault
and be apologetic, which I am, and,
on top of that, I just...
Look, Ralph...
Mr. Seeger, I just...
I really need to get out there.
I need to do good.
I promise,
if you give me that opportunity,
I'm not gonna mess it up.
One last chance.
Now that we, uh, got that part settled,
I'm gonna go freshen up my coffee
and let you gentlemen cross those T's.
That's a great guy. Great guy.
Really appreciate this second chance.
I don't know what the hell
that man sees in you, Jablonski.
I mean, I know you served together,
but, frankly, I don't care.
I've made it my life's work keeping
cowboys like you out of the Union,
so I'll be watching you.
♪ Every step you make ♪
♪ Every shit you take ♪
- ♪ Every time you.. ♪
- Everything good?
Quite.
Fill these out, all of them.
Once you pay your initial dues,
we'll get you started
on the health care plan.
There's dental included, right?
After a probationary period lasting...
30 days.
Come on, man. Three days.
Two weeks.
One.
Fine.
With a Union rep
accompanying him in the field.
- Generous. Thank you.
- Great.
All right. Thanks, and, uh...
...I
want the night shift.
- Not on my life.
- Come on, Seeger.
- That's where the big money is!
- No. Not a chance.
Amount of shit
you stirred up working night shift,
you expect me to let you back
out there where the sun don't shine?
Fine.
Day shift.
Good. Anything else?
No.
Oh, yeah. I got some,
uh, teeth I need to sell.
Go to the cage.
Seeger, thank you kindly.
Mm-hmm.
And remember, Bud,
one last strike.
Is... Are you referring to bowling,
because...
- I'm saying there's a strike in bowl..
- You're back. That's all that matters.
Carol.
Carol, did you eat my yogurt again?
I even wrote my name on the lid today,
so you literally had to peel back
my name to get to the yogurt.
Oh, what? You can't hear me?
I'm gonna fart in my yogurt,
and you're gonna eat my fart.
Next.
Mr. Jablonski?
Yeah. Teeth.
So I look at it like this. I get
back out there, do what I gotta do,
you know, for Mr. Mullet.
This is chipped, female.
Appears to be an almost Elder,
roughly 90 years old.
Ninety? You probably need
to check that again.
- You sure it's 90?
- I'm sure.
Huh.
Okay, whatever.
Full price still, right?
I'm sorry. Code 107 in the book
clearly states anything..
Enough of the codes. It's fine.
- That's the net for the teeth.
- Yeah, I'll come in... Hey!
However, due to
the truncated processing time,
Mr. Seeger would like me to inform you
we need your dues up front,
which, of course, is $5,000.
$5,000? I thought it was two?
Those are 2017 rates, Mr. Jablonski.
Then there is 15%
off the top of every fang,
and we have to hold 50%
until we receive your paperwork.
And, of course, $10
for your membership card,
which gets you one free app
at Cheesecake Factory.
- I don't like cheesecake.
- Do you have that?
Why won't you take the $10 out of that?
Taking everything else.
You don't have cash on you?
You really wanna make me split this?
Okay, you are good to go.
Am I?
If you have any issues with this,
Carol right here would be happy
to further assist you.
Oh, great. I see you met your Union rep.
Huh.
What?
Come on, Bud.
Sir, please.
That new girl's a smoke show.
Right, but I'm begging you to
reconsider. I'm not meant for the field.
I just bought an ergonomic chair with
my own money. I'm all in on the desk.
That's why I need
you out there with him.
Right? Someone who knows
the codes to the letter.
- Okay, but..
- Hey, hey, hey.
Do you wanna move up here?
You gotta get your ass
out in the field. All right?
Think about it this way,
you're gonna be
my eyes and ears, my friend.
- Right?
- Right..
And the minute he messes up,
the minute he goes against code,
you'll be there
reporting it back to me, right?
The sooner he fucks up,
the sooner
your sweet cheeks are in Carol's desk.
You work out?
- A little.
- Yeah, thought so.
♪ I remember ♪
♪ When I was just a bad little boy ♪
♪ My momma used to tell me, "Son,
they gonna read just what you say" ♪
You're late.
Close it.
I was actually here an hour ago,
but you weren't,
so I went to go get us breakfast.
I got you an organic,
gluten-free, paleo bran muffin.
Really? Thank you.
- I was starving.
- That was a six-dollar muffin.
- What do you have on?
- What?
- What are you wearing?
- Just, like, normal clothes.
The handbook says blend in on the hunt.
Be inconspicuous.
You have on a suit.
How's that inconspicuous?
We're in the Valley. In the summertime.
- It's a summery suit.
- A summery suit?
- Juniper green. Yes.
- What is juniper green?
A hue of green I found to be
complementary against my skin tone.
Whatever it is, don't wear it again.
Look, I'll put myself together,
and we'll take off, all right?
- Do you have somewhere I can hang this?
- Yep.
Not there.
I'll just... hold on to it.
This ain't gonna last.
Got enough weapons and ammo in here
to take down El Jefe, huh?
What you know about El Jefe?
Oh, come on.
Legendary 700-year-old European vampire.
Some say he's
at the top of the LA drug trade,
just waiting for his moment to reemerge.
Fangs so sharp, with just one,
you could buy a mansion in Bel Air.
Hmm.
You sound like Big John.
Whole lot of gibberish.
You know that's a crock of shit, right?
I didn't take you for
an arts and crafts guy.
- What are these all about?
- Wanna keep your hands off my shit?
It's my trophy case.
For each one that I kill, I, uh...
They're already dead,
but you get my drift.
'Cause they're allergic to wood. Smart.
They're allergic to wood,
but not just any wood. It's mpingo wood.
The strongest African hardwood.
Not that Ikea shit.
We mix it with the garlic.
The wooden bullets pierce the heart.
- The silver..
- Silver to the throat. Right.
Yeah. Cuts the head off... usually.
Usually. Right, you are
referring to Uber Vamps,
who have come back from decapitation.
Not if you blast the heart with wood
before you cut their throats with silver.
Mm-hmm. You also forgot to mention
that you can kill them by burning them.
I didn't forget anything.
That's how I get my money.
Why would I burn the fangs?
I don't do that.
Listen, Guacamole Suit,
right there on the shelf,
grab that for me.
Get that, we'll take off.
And remember, whatever you do, don't...
drop my shit.
So, uh, where we going?
I'm going hunting. I
don't know about you.
♪ All my life,
been grindin' all my life ♪
♪ Sacrificed, hustle paid the price ♪
♪ Want a slice? Got to roll the dice ♪
♪ That's why, all my life
I been grindin' all my life... ♪
Why you wearing the seat belt like that?
Um, yeah,
I mean, usually the seat belts aren't
like this complicated and heavy. But..
It's not complicated.
It's just a seat belt. It protects you.
Sure.
Sure. It's still protecting me though.
If anything happened, it's just..
See? It still catches me.
I see.
It's gonna be a long day.
♪ Sacrificed, hustle paid the price ♪
♪ Want a slice? Got to roll the dice ♪
♪ That's why, all my life
I been grindin' all my life ♪
So, are you gonna tell me
what we're doing at an animal shelter?
I'm gonna tell you shit.
What you know about Juvies?
Juvies or Juveniles, AKA Zombie Vamps,
formed when an already young vamp
turns somebody else.
Instead of the strength of a full vamp,
they lack regenerative abilities
and appear more dead than alive.
They can't process human blood yet,
so what do they do?
- I'm aware.
- They feed off of small animals, rodents.
So you've read the book?
I don't have to read it. I'm out here.
What do you know
about different species of vampires?
I know there are five types.
Southern, Eastern,
Spider, Uber, and Juvenile.
They are largely solitary,
but when together, there is a hierarchy.
They organize by age. What else?
The sunlight is the only thing
they're scared of.
They can't reproduce,
but they can turn people.
Should I continue?
- What about familiars?
- You think this guy's one of them?
I don't know. You tell me.
- Hmm?
- I think he fits the profile.
- You think so?
- Absolutely.
More powerful vamps
have more powerful familiars.
And when it comes to Juvies,
a little kid like this,
he's probably grabbing those
cats for 'em, try to get 'em turned.
- Oh man.
- What?
No, I'm just a big cat lover.
I got two of them myself.
Oh. Okay.
Well, that explains it.
- Want to see a picture?
- No, I don't.
Maybe later.
All right. Here we go.
There's his car.
Canoga Bowl. Closed for 18 months.
It's perfect.
- Can I offer some advice?
- No.
I mean, economically speaking,
why go after Juvies?
Why not let them ripen,
come back when their teeth are valuable?
I could come back in September,
but right now, I'm out of time.
And beggars can't be choosers.
Plus, you don't want
these things biting people, do you?
Wait. Why don't you have time?
- Why you ask me so many questions?
- I'm just..
Just stay in the truck
and do your business.
Stay in the truck? No, I have to be
with you at all times in the field.
- Union rules.
- Other than keeping you alive,
I don't give a shit about rules.
No, no, you don't understand. All times.
You're gonna stay in this car.
With that in mind, here.
- What? No, I don't believe in guns.
- You don't believe in 'em?
No, they're amoral.
They're killing machines.
They're not for me.
When I was a kid, I tried
shooting a squirrel with a BB gun,
and I just couldn't. All right?
I still have nightmares
where I can see his little face
making little squirrel noises,
and I still have nightmares about it.
Made squirrel noises, huh?
- What does a squirrel noise sound like?
- It's like...
Whatever! I don't wanna talk about it.
Stay in the truck.
It's impossible.
How the hell can you be here?
It's daytime.
You've been a bad boy, Troy.
Did you know that a vampire
cannot live without its fangs?
And yet, for whatever reason,
whatever cruel joke from the gods...
they are the one thing
we cannot regenerate.
Everything that makes
a vampire a predator
is in its fangs.
Each set is a life
that could have lived a thousand lives.
Lives that you had a part in ending.
Yet it wasn't always like this,
you know?
There was a time when you humans,
you worshiped us as gods.
Right here in this valley, you built
temples of blood and bone to honor us.
And then you turned on us.
Well, guess what?
I'm gonna take back what's ours,
one property at a time.
The way I see it,
you have two choices, two doors.
One, you bend the knee
and join me in service, and you live.
And two...
you don't.
All right.
So, what the hell do you want? Huh?
Who brought you this tooth?
A name.
You're so full of shit, lady.
You think you're a god?
You're not gods. You're a big mistake.
You're a genetic mutation
that would've died out
if there hadn't been a stinking hole
for y'all to crawl into.
Door number two it is.
No. No!
No!
Time for the tooth fairy.
Ah!
♪ Look at this photograph
Every time I do, it makes me laugh ♪
Hello, sir.
How are we on this fine morning?
Any violations to report?
He is certainly heading that way,
but nothing verified quite yet.
Well, where is he now?
He left me in the car
and went into a bowling alley.
You didn't follow him?
I thought he was gonna shoot me!
He's very difficult to reason with, sir.
Kid! You want your promotion?
You want Carol's desk?
Then get off your ass, get in there,
and verify those violations.
Ugh! Hair on your nipples!
- Bud?
- Seth!
- Shit.
- Bud!
- Hurry up! Shoot it!
I... I don't have my gun!
Give me my shotgun!
I'm... I'm just an observer!
Your gonna be hors d'œuvre
if you don't give me that gun!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Whoa! I'm sorry!
Next time I tell you, "Gimme that
goddamn gun," you gimme that goddamn gun!
- Now duck!
- What?
I said duck!
You okay?
Oh, jeez. That was horrible.
These Juvie teeth ain't worth shit,
but get enough of 'em...
It's a number game like you said.
Uh, you okay?
What's going on?
Oh, come on. No, no, I'm not okay.
- All right? Look at me!
- What?
Vampires just tried to kill me.
You put a gun in my face,
and now I just pissed
my favorite fucking suit!
Hey, hey. Relax. You did good in there.
You did good in there.
Besides, everybody pisses themselves
the first time.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Did you?
- No, I... No, I didn't. But listen, you did.
Here,
dry your eyes. Dry your eyes, okay.
You know what?
Put it on me. My bad. We bit off
more than we could chew today.
So why don't we go home, get some rest.
In the morning,
we'll kick some motherfucking ass. Okay?
- Okay.
- All right, come on.
Let's get in the car.
What the fuck is that?
What'd you eat today?
You know what?
Let's have you get in the back.
Don't want you
to get that on my vintage seats.
- What, are you serious?
- Damn right.
Come on. Gotta move.
Hang your leg out the back
so we can air dry.
Hey. Hey!
- You forgot your man-purse.
- Wait. That's expens..
You gotta get some of this too.
I'm sure you know, Mr. Union Man.
But when vamps are killed,
they release a gas that gets on you
that other vamps can sniff out.
So you gotta get all of that off.
Here, take this.
It's my special blend,
like a little, uh, skunk musk, okay?
- Now, get that on you, in the shower.
- Oh Jesus.
On every inch of you, okay?
Be extremely careful.
Don't get it in your eyes.
And whatever you do,
don't get it in your butthole.
What happens in the butthole?
I mean, it can't kill you, but...
Jesus Christ.
By the way, lock your doors,
don't come out after dark, and, uh...
- Guess what?
- What?
You're dried up.
Oh!
- Oh God. It's okay.
- I'm sorry about that.
- No, no, me. I got it.
- It's okay.
It's my fault.
I couldn't see over my baskets.
I got it. This is a...
You a... you a doctor?
Uh, nurse, actually.
Hope you don't think this is weird,
but you got a lot of scrubs.
Yeah, I mean, I hate doing laundry,
so I kind of just kept buying new ones.
- Got out of control.
- Okay.
But, hey, new apartment.
Why not start off on the right foot?
Yeah. Well, welcome to the building.
I'm right there in 20.
- Oh! Well, I'm Heather. I'm in 19.
- Well, I'm Bud 20.
Can you help me with that, actually?
Oh. Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
- You can just put that down anywhere.
- Sure. Okay.
- See you've got a retro vibe poppin', huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- Dig that.
- Thanks.
I wish I had a beer
or something to offer you.
Uh, a previous tenant left some ice cream
in the freezer, if you're interested.
No, thanks. I'll take a rain check.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Welcome to the building.
Thank you.
Feeling better?
Not really.
Got a little bit of that
yellow stuff in my butthole.
It was so much worse
than what you even described.
Bet it was.
You looking for something?
- Whoa. Hey, that's personal.
- No, no, no.
"Violation code 101, terminated vamps
and didn't report to the Union."
"Violation code 276, breaking and
entering without Union sanctions."
- That did happen.
- Violation. Violation. Violation.
Oh, look at this. "Needs to reimburse me
for six-dollar muffin"?
It's a standard part of Union procedure.
- I have to document everything.
- It's not.
It's for Seeger to keep me
out the Union. Ain't that great?
You almost got me killed yesterday.
You almost got
yourself killed yesterday.
I told you stay your punk-ass in
the car. That's why I work by myself.
Listen. What? You're gonna die
in the name of kissing your boss's ass?
Well, he didn't give me a choice, okay?
Listen to me, Mr. Union Fellow.
I may not follow all the Union rules,
but let me tell you something.
If we went by the book,
we'd both be dead by now!
And you saw that yesterday.
Look. Just give me a couple of days.
Okay, a couple days.
So, what's on the agenda today?
Like every day.
Hunting vampires.
Bud, what are we
doing at a pawn shop?
This dude's cheap as shit, but
he got goods we need in order to, uh...
What the hell?
Oh Jesus.
Shut up. Shut up.
Hey, hey.
Don't you puke in here! Don't
touch nothing. Don't leave your DNA.
I swallowed it.
Troy.
Troy?
Damn it.
Wait, is that...
It was.
Oh no.
Who... who does that?
All right, we gotta move.
Wait a minute. Take this.
Ow!
Are you kidding me?
- It's not right, okay. Wait..
- Damn right. How you think he feels, huh?
Come on, let's go.
Wait. You can't leave.
That's against protocol.
We have to call the Union
and wait for them.
- Code 233 says any hunter who encounters...
- Code? I don't give a shit.
...suspicious civilian death
will be under a 30-day suspension..
We don't have 30
days. I don't give fuck!
We gotta leave. There's other
vamps around here. Let's go.
No, no. I'm calling.
Whoa! We have dead humans here.
We have to report this.
That ain't no dead human!
That's my friend!
Listen, I'm not telling you
you cannot report it.
I'm just telling you to delay it.
We'll make an anonymous call
to the cops, and, after 24 hours,
you can make
your funky little report. Let's go!
Why do you care?
What difference does a day make?
I'm gonna lose my family in a day!
That's the difference!
What?
Look, if I don't score some prices
at Union wages by Monday,
my wife and my daughter move to Florida.
That means, if you call Seeger,
I'm gonna lose my family.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Yeah, I bet you are.
So what you're saying
is you... you kinda need me.
But...
No, I didn't... I didn't say I need you.
I didn't say that.
- No, I just mean...
- I didn't say that.
You told me your secrets.
I'm gonna break protocol for you.
- So we're like a team, partners, whatever.
- I didn't say partners.
- Crockett and Tubbs.
- No.
- Any partnership you find satisfactory.
- Listen.
What I'm saying is this,
is as a man,
just give me till the weekend.
Yeah, okay. Until the weekend.
Yeah.
Look. What do you want me to do?
If I keep... he's gonna suspect something.
Just relax.
I got a tip on this house
from Big J.
Why don't you
check the glove box right now?
Yeah.
That's what we're doing right there.
That's what we doing.
These... garlic grenades.
Pull the pin, garlic and sawdust
comes out, clears the room.
I think. Haven't actually had to use it.
But, in theory,
that's what's gonna happen.
An unproven weapon
for my first real vampire fight.
- That's wonderful. Thank you.
- Shit. Shit!
What? What?
Goddamn Nazarian Brothers.
Wait, the Nazarian brothers.
Oh, they're big-time hunters.
Yeah, not bigger than me though.
They cleared out all of Glendale.
Now they're headed west.
Hey, Bud.
I thought I smelled chlorine.
Funny.
Thought I smelled shit.
- Who's the cupcake?
- Seth.
I'm his Union rep. But you can
call me Cupcake or whatever you prefer.
- I'm a big fan, by the way.
- Want to get a selfie for your Instagram?
What you guys doing in Simi Valley?
You know what we're doing here, bro.
We let you do the hard part for us,
figure out which house
is hiding the goods, then, you know.
You got me twisted. I did the work,
but I ain't do it for you.
Oh, come on, Bud. Think about it.
Waste a week waiting for the right
moment that we just might take from you?
Or we run up there in force right now.
Sack the place together.
Split the money down the middle.
Well, one, ain't nobody
taking shit from me.
And two...
Yeah. It's a good idea.
Wanna get a selfie?
Right now? Is that appropriate?
- We can wait..
- That's not appropriate at all.
- What's this?
- Keep your neck from getting chewed out.
Take this. Stay behind me.
I keep you alive.
Don't shoot where they are.
Shoot where they're gonna be.
You ready? Let's go.
♪ Ooh, baby, I like it raw
Yeah, baby, I like it raw ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, I like it raw
♪ Shimmy shimmy ya
Shimmy yam, shimmy yay ♪
♪ Gimme the mic so
I can take it away ♪
♪ Off on a natural charge,
bon voyage ♪
♪ Yeah, from the home of the Dodgers
Brooklyn squad ♪
♪ Wu-Tang Killer Bees on a swarm ♪
♪ Rain on ya college ass disco dorm ♪
♪ For you to even touch my skill ♪
♪ You gotta have the one killer Bee
And he ain't gonna kill now... ♪
What's the garlic for?
Any vamp gets close to me,
I spit in their eye,
melt hole in their fucking head.
Bro, you got any more gum?
- You always share that with your brother?
- We share everything.
D, you're supposed
to pry that shit open, not smash it.
Hey. Are we inside the house or not,
bro?
Don't even think about it.
Got him.
Nice shot, bro.
Time to get paid.
Open up.
I told him not to do it.
- Really?
- I'm sorry.
- Put that gun down.
- Okay.
- Take your finger off the trigger.
- Right. Okay.
Just watch my six.
Six... Uh...
- It's a hive.
- What?
Showtime, bro.
Head on out.
Bitch-ass.
Keep your head on a swivel, all right?
And stay away from the walls.
Oh shit! Bud!
Bud! I don't... What do I do?
Ah! You gotta stop wiggling!
Oh no!
No!
Oh shit! The gun's broken!
- Take the safety off!
- Help, Bud! My gun's not working.
Oh, come on!
Oh God!
Ah!
Buckshot mouthwash, baby.
Nice, bro. Yes.
I got six.
You got six. I got five.
I'll catch you up.
Oh shit! Bud, help me!
Wait, hold up! Wait, hold on! Ah!
Don't let it bite you, Seth!
Haircut time, bro.
I'm out!
Ah!
Bud, help me! Bud, help!
This motherfucker
threw me up the stairs?
Ah!
Bro, send one!
No good!
Nice work, bro.
Help! Help me!
Seth, my shotgun!
- Big money, baby.
- Huh? This is what I was talking about.
- This was good, yes?
- Very good.
What happened to you?
You piss your pants?
It's kinda my thing.
- Bro.
- What you doing? What're you doing?
Listen, pee-pee pants,
this is man's world, not little boy.
Gonna get you a Pamper.
Anyway, listen. Be safe, man. Okay?
I'mma take this and put it towards
my baby girl's tuition, you know?
That's why I'm out here. You know...
Familiar on the run.
I got it.
- He's up again. That was vampire.
- I know.
Streets done changed.
I hear they got this sunscreen
that they put on.
It's real thick, and they can now last
out in the sunlight like 15, 20 minutes.
You know it's made
from the shell of desert tortoise.
It's illegal in 40 countries,
right, bro?
Vampire sunscreen? The Valley?
I don't like the sound of this.
- Hey, wait, this doesn't make sense.
- 'Sup?
Okay, that's a Spider,
but that's an Uber.
Those are Southerns, and...
Yeah, that's an Eastern.
You can tell by his fangs in the front.
Ain't Bloods and Crips.
It's the Valley. They cross-pollinate.
No, these vamps would never
choose to live together.
Ubers are solo-nesters.
Spiders cohabitate,
but never with Easterns and Southerns.
- They'd steal their food.
- Listen to this kid. Huh?
This joker reads a few books,
he thinks he knows more than the pros.
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
Kid makes a good point.
But...
But I'm outta time. I gotta go
pick up the little one. Come on.
Pull these fangs. And why don't you go
to the bathroom and dry off your dick.
You okay?
I don't know.
I just keep thinking about
how all those vampires we just killed
used to be regular people.
There you go.
The old
vampires-are-just-like-us routine.
But they're not, Seth.
You know what I see when I see a vamp?
Big old dollar signs.
'Cause all they are
is murderers and liars.
It ain't Brad Pitt in a leather jacket
and some blood raves.
It's not Eclipse. It's not New Moon.
It's not Breaking Dawn Part One.
It ain't like that, all right?
Why do you know the names
to all the specific Twilight films?
What's your gripe
with Breaking Dawn Part 2?
It's the exciting conclusion
of the whole Twilight Saga.
Wha... Have you seen Part 2?
Bella has her baby now. It's insane.
- She had the baby?
- Oh, I wish I was you!
To experience that the first time.
You're in for a treat.
My daughter hipped me to all that.
I don't really get into all that.
But you got something different, Seth.
You're tougher than you think you are.
No.
I'm serious.
You're just saying that
so I don't report you to Seeger.
No, I'm not. You got what it takes.
I'm telling you. You have that instinct.
You could be a real hunter out here.
Telling you right now.
Fuck Carol.
Fuck accounting.
You could do this.
- Hey. Hey!
- Hi, Dad!
- Dad? What happened to "Daddy"?
- Little kids say, "Daddy."
Oh, is that right? "Dad," huh?
Everything's changing around here.
You're late. Again.
So, what is all this?
Well, I can't actually sell the house
without putting it on the market.
Yeah. Last I checked,
it's three days until Monday.
Come on, Dad.
We're gonna be late to the party.
You know, I was thinking,
what if we don't go?
What if we stay here at the house
and eat pizza, some ice cream..
Bud. No. She's been talking about this
all week. You promised.
Yeah, well, I just didn't think
it was the right time right now.
What? Okay, give me a reason why.
Right. So, Daddy was just kidding.
He was just being weird.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you guys are going to a party!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right.
- See, Daddy was just being strange.
- Strange, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Bye.
- Bye, baby.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday... ♪
- Cake time, baby. I'll check on the kids.
- All right.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Hello?
I've been looking for you, Bud.
Who is this?
Troy spoke so highly of you.
Your name was the last thing
on his lips when he died.
You know how this ends, don't you?
You tell me.
With you on your knees in front of me,
begging for the lives
of your wife and your daughter.
You took something from me, and now
I'm gonna take everything from you.
Enjoy the party.
Yay!
Aw. Nice. Ha ha. That's so nice.
We gotta go, baby. That's so nice.
- Happy birthday.
- Bye, Paige.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Up, up, up.
Look, buckle yourself in, okay?
Look, in here, all right.
Now let's put your headphones on, okay?
Got your iPad right here.
Now listen. Dad's gonna be driving.
You might feel a little swerving,
but that's just my special driving.
Just pick up, pick up, pick up.
Can't talk. Meeting a realtor.
- Don't hang up!
- Why? Is Paige okay?
Uh, yeah, she's great, but, uh...
Look, Joss, we're in trouble, okay?
All of us.
What? What are you talking about?
There's a lot I need to tell you.
I know you've had trouble
trusting me in the past.
I know you think I keep things from you,
but right now, you gotta trust me.
- I don't want to lose either of you.
- Now you're freaking me out.
Pack your bags, be ready to go,
and I will explain everything, okay?
A bag?
All right.
Hey. You took your headphones off, huh?
I already won my race.
Besides, looks like you can use my help.
Uh, you're not wrong on that.
Light!
Whoa!
Car!
Thank you!
All right, big jump. Big jump!
Woo-hoo!
There's a guy on the right!
Hold on.
Cover your ears, sweetie.
That was awesome.
Yeah? Just don't tell your mother.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Come on. All right. Come on. Let's run.
- You ever heard of Jackie Joyner-Kersee?
- Uh, no.
- I'll show her to you.
- Okay.
No! No! No!
No!
No, no, no! Stop!
Hola, Bud.
I told you you'd be on your knees
begging for their lives.
It's okay. It's okay.
So beg.
- Go to hell.
- Oh, your compadre said the same thing.
Oh shit. Baby, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for this, Joss. Are you okay?
Yeah.
What is happening, Bud?
I could try to explain it right now,
but it's not gonna make any sense.
- But..
- But what?
I'm not exactly a pool cleaner.
Well, then, what are you?
I...
hunt vampires.
- What?
- Yeah. I hunt vampires.
- Vampires?
- Yeah. That's what I do.
- Yeah.
Okay, so all of the lies, all of the
late-night calls, all of the locks...
Come on, man.
The reason I'm separated
from the man I love is vampires? Ow!
Stop choking her like that!
Come on, Bud. We said
we were gonna be honest with each other.
We are.
- I know. Don't look at it.
- Oh my God!
Listen...
I wanted to tell you.
I just didn't know how.
Okay. Okay, so...
Uh, what do you want?
What do I want?
You and your daughter.
- They're not a part of this!
- Pendejo, you made them a part of it!
- Don't touch me!
- Don't touch her!
I'm not afraid of you.
Such a brave muñeca.
Take them.
- No! No!
- No, don't touch her!
- Leave her alone! Get your hands off her!
- Don't touch her!
I'll come get you!
Daddy!
- I'mma fix all of this. I love y'all!
- Cálmate, Bud.
A new day is dawning,
and your little girl's
gonna be a part of it.
Get off of me.
First, I'm gonna turn her,
and then I'm gonna watch
as she drinks your wife.
I wish
you could be there to see it,
but I'm afraid
someone's having you for dinner.
Daddy!
Oh, I'm alive.
Oh, Bud.
Oh!
Oh, I feel weird.
Yeah, I bet... I bet you do.
What happened to me?
Just some bullshit.
You know how shit go.
But, uh...
You probably wanna... check your teeth.
Check my teeth?
Yeah, just check them.
There's a mirror over there.
Oh...
Oh! Oh no!
Oh no. Oh, that's not good.
- What! That was totally involuntary.
- It's like a hiccup, probably.
I'm sorry, man, it was all my fault.
How you feel?
Pretty horrified
about the fact that I'm a vampire.
- Right. Right.
- But also like...
- I don't know, kind of amazing.
- Yeah, like..
Like my blood, it just...
it feels like it's on fire..
Like you had, like,
a lot of energy drinks.
Oh, I can smell everything!
Oh God, did I shit myself this time?
No, no, no, you look fine.
- Is there like a mark?
- No, you look good.
Everything looks great.
Listen, let's just take it easy.
We're gonna work this out.
Oh wow.
Mainly I just...
Whoa, I just feel
hungry!
Goddamn it, Seth.
I'm sorry, kid.
I'm actually gonna miss you, man,
you know?
It's crazy how
you get attached to someone.
Oh shit.
Bud?
Huh?
You cut my head off.
I thought we were friends.
I... You rushed me.
It's just reaction. That's what I do.
It's in my blood. It's like...
You ever see Tyson? He...
You don't walk up on Tyson either.
Friendship is complicated, huh?
Yeah, friendships are complicated.
All right, wait. Follow my voice.
Left, there. Yep, okay.
Easy. No. Okay, easy, easy.
Okay, here we go.
The fuck?
Okay, gentle.
Gentle.
Huh. Still fits.
Wha...
Oh, it's been quite the week.
Yeah, it has. You good?
- How do I look?
- You look all right.
- You feel all right?
- You swear?
Yeah.
- Hey!
- Sorry. Just kidding.
- Okay. All right.
- Too soon. Too soon. All right.
Hey, I'm sorry I tried to eat you.
How 'bout we not report this
to Seeger until Monday?
Seeger, shit. Oh, what?
You don't think he's gonna notice?
What, am I just supposed to
wear turtlenecks from now on?
I mean, I do look good in a T-neck,
but that's not sustainable.
- Wait. Where are we going?
- Going to get my family back.
I have to stop at my place
and get some information.
What's going on with your neck?
Is it repairing itself?
I actually think it is.
Okay, just be careful.
Don't go over any speed bumps.
Damn. Damn.
My bad.
You have a driving problem.
You know that, right?
I gotta go to apartment 19.
I'll be back in five.
Heather, you just moved in.
Leaving so soon?
Bud, just listen to me.
Look, we need to talk.
Talk? Vampires kidnapped my family.
You wanna talk?
- I didn't have a choice.
- I don't give a rat's ass.
This is stupid, Bud.
Let me at least explain.
Okay, listen.
Because of you, my family got kidnapped,
and my friend is dead.
Or undead.
So I don't want no problems, I just...
That's what she does, Bud.
She turns people against their will.
I wasn't even a familiar.
She just... just did this to me.
You think I wanna
work for a monster like her?
Then why do you?
- She's my maker, okay?
- What?
And an Uber Vamp.
Look, she forced me to get close to you.
She wanted to get back at you
for what you did to her.
What you talking about?
She just...
She just wanted to know how to hurt you.
Why?
So, you just gonna
light your finger on fire, huh?
You killed a vampire Monday, didn't you?
- Sweet old lady?
- Not so sweet, actually.
That was Audrey's daughter.
Daughter? How?
When she came over, she had
a little girl she had to leave behind.
So by the time they went back,
found her, and turned her, she was old.
- And I killed her.
- And you killed her.
And now they got Paige and Jocelyn.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Bud. I don't feel so good.
Could you hold my head for a little?
Holy shit.
You're walking on sacred ground.
You should be honored.
Where are you taking us?
- Why, are you frightened?
- No.
You should be.
Well, then you don't know me
that well, bitch. Ah!
Why are you doing this?
Paige, don't talk to her.
She has a right to know.
You don't get to decide..
I had a daughter once, feisty like you.
I wanted to make a better world for her.
A world where
she could be free from hiding.
But your father took that away from me.
Now, you see,
it's only fair I take you away from him.
If you hurt her, I'll kill you.
But I'm already dead.
I'm not gonna hurt her, Ms. Jablonski.
I'm gonna make sure
no one can ever hurt her again.
You should thank me.
A war is coming,
and your little girl's
gonna be on the winning side.
- No!
- Paige!
Let me go!
No. No!
Come on.
Seth, hold your head still.
Looks like they've turned him
with Uber blood,
so he'll be unpredictable for a while.
He'll get under control eventually.
Here.
No, I'm pescatarian.
Come on.
- Mm. Mmm!
- There we go.
Mmm.
You hunters are always
complaining about LA running dry.
That's what Audrey's trying to change.
It's, like, sweet but a little tangy.
That's nice.
Oh yeah, get inside of me.
She uses her cover as a realtor
to buy properties all over the Valley
and move vamps
back in amongst the rest of us.
Within a year, all vamp activity in LA
will be traceable
to her sitting at the top.
Not if I get to her first.
I'll lead the way.
- All right, I'm coming too.
- No, no, no. No. Hell no, Seth.
You got too much energy now.
You fresh off some blood.
I don't want you to switch up on me,
try to bite my kidneys out.
No, Bud, listen. They tortured me.
Okay, they drank my blood.
They cut my head off.
I guess technically, you cut my head
off, but they turned me into this, okay?
- I want to help take her down.
- Okay.
We'll get you changed,
head back to my spot, and we'll gear up.
- Oh, right now?
- Yeah, right now.
What? It's dark out.
That's a suicide mission.
Welcome to the
motherfucking night shift.
♪ Body Count, Body Count
Body Count, Body Count ♪
♪ Yeah motherfucker! ♪
♪ Body Count, Body Count
Body Count, Body Count ♪
♪ Body Count's in the house, Body Count
Body Count's in the house, Body Count ♪
Oh shit!
- Ah! Oh, they got me!
- Look, Seth, calm down!
They're expecting humans.
It's lead. It can't hurt you.
- Really?
- Yes. But, hey, let it make you mad.
♪ Body Count ♪
♪ Body Count's in the house,
Body Count ♪
♪ Body Count's in the house... ♪
Ah!
♪ Body Count's in the house,
Body Count ♪
You okay?
This one actually hurts. Shit. Ah! Ah!
Bud, what do we do?
We're surrounded.
Black Cowboy.
Get down.
Oh shit.
How the hell you get here?
The snowflake.
I might have texted him.
- Welcome to the fucking Union, brother.
- Thank you.
- Hey, hey, if you don't get your ass off..
- Oh. Sorry.
- This way.
- Sorry.
Come on, Big J.
After you.
Bud, in the back, look for the staircase.
That's the entrance to her tunnel.
Keep going down, and you'll find her.
There's a faster way down,
but you wouldn't survive it.
We survive everything.
See me fighting a bear,
you pour honey on me.
You two go ahead. We'll catch up.
Come on. Let's get cracking.
Just like old times.
I'm out.
Look at this shit here. Jackpot.
Man, look at all this gear.
Okay.
Ugh. Shit, look at this.
All this sunscreen.
Vamps runnin' around in the day.
She could take over the Valley.
Handle him, J!
Okay.
Oh shit.
I see you. He didn't know, did he?
He didn't know.
Whoo! Get him, J.
Stay down, fool.
Yo. You did that
without even stretching, huh?
That was my weak leg.
See all this? Huh?
All these guns?
Check it out.
Silver-tipped wooden bullets.
Vampire killers.
What's that about?
Is she El Jefe?
Nah. El Jefe is bigger than this,
brother.
But, either way,
that bitch got an ass-whooping coming.
Yeah.
Yeah, they down here.
Let's get cracking.
Just like old times.
He's coming.
I can smell him.
I don't know how all this works,
but I know my husband,
and he's gonna murder you.
- Ex-husband.
- See, now you're just being a bitch.
Bring him to me.
Paige.
- This place ain't creepy at all.
- Tell me about it.
Here we go.
Bud!
Jablonski...
John!
That's how we do, baby.
You know how we do.
We bag 'em, and we tag 'em.
That's how we get it done.
What's going on with you?
Ain't nothing going on.
Ain't nothing wrong with me, man.
- You all right?
- Shit. You know they can't fuck with me.
Okay, but why you leaning like that?
We been battle-tested.
This don't mean nothing.
- All right.
- Nothing but a flesh wound, dog.
Okay. Still, it don't look too good.
Come on, let's get up out of here.
Come on. We ain't got much time.
Gotta get you out of here. Come on, man.
Come on!
- Big John, what the hell is you doing?
- I'm saving your Black ass.
What are you talking about?
Go get your family
right now. I got this.
- We can't do it like this.
- You know I work alone.
- You crazy motherfucker.
- Go.
- You better stay alive.
- Go!
I'll be here waiting for you!
All right, motherfuckers, come on!
West side for life!
John...
I'm not supposed to kill you yet,
but you've been a real pain in the ass,
so give me one good reason.
Burn in hell.
Good enough.
- You're working on that landing, huh?
- No, I planned it like that.
Go, we've got him.
No!
Paige! Stay back.
Daddy!
- Joss, you okay?
- Yeah.
All right. I'll let you go.
A life for a life
or whatever the hell you have.
You took my daughter, Jablonski.
- I'm just returning the favor.
- No.
- Mommy!
- Baby!
What do you think, muñeca?
I'm gonna kill your daddy,
then I'm gonna make you
drink your mean old mommy,
and then I'm gonna be
your new, improved mommy.
How does that sound?
I hate you!
That's not very nice.
I hate you too.
Daddy!
Ah!
I should've just got another job.
- Baby, get up!
- Come on, Daddy, get up!
Baby, I'm trying.
- Try harder.
- Oh, okay.
In the end,
the devil comes for everyone.
That's what you get.
Bitch.
No!
Mommy!
Pull!
Wood to the heart, silver to the neck.
Your last bullet, cabrón?
No!
Fucking pool boy.
The best.
Y'all good?
Works every time.
Let's go.
Come on, babe. Let's go.
All right.
- Hey. Where's Seth?
- Hey.
- Whoa!
- No, no, no. Babe, babe, no.
They're the good vampires.
That's my girl Heather.
That's my guy Seth.
-Hey.
Whose arm is that?
Oh. Sorry.
But, Bud... got my first pair of fangs.
Whoa.
That's big money right there.
- Guess what?
- What's that?
I didn't pee myself this time.
- Get out.
- Vampires don't pee or poop.
Nah, they don't.
- Please let me have this little victory.
- Of course you can. C'mon. Let's go.
Do they really not pee or poop?
- Does that mean they're full of shit?
- Language!
Big John.
I'll miss you, baby.
Oh, no.
Go ahead. Come on.
It's got good energy in that.
All right.
We were hiding right over there.
Right over there.
Jablonski!
Seeger? What the hell you doing,
walking all fast like that?
New shoe boots on.
And you. What are you, sick?
- Uh, pink eye.
- What?
It's when poo particles get in your eye.
Where's Big John?
Oh goddamn it!
I did you a solid.
But now you have
graciously returned the favor
because after the shit
you pulled here tonight,
I'll never have to deal with you again.
For starters,
flagrantly violating code 682,
operating outside of your shift.
Actually, sir, if I may.
Code 741 states that,
"If a hunter is in a 911 situation,"
he may circumvent normal operating hours
"so long as he notifies the Union
before entering," which he did.
Thank you. Thank you for that.
There's also code 584,
unlawful termination of familiars
without prior authorization.
Yes, sir, that is correct,
but Section 4 states,
"When fired on, a hunter is
lawfully allowed to return fire,"
which is what happened here.
Code 424, "A Union hunter
must make all reasonable efforts
to limit collateral damage to property
while engaging in a hunt."
Boom!
- Sir, code 42..
- I got this.
Code 424 was rescinded by
the national office in January.
Boom. Boom.
- Someone's been reading.
- Saw it in the newsletter.
Yeah. I see what's going on here.
Uh-huh.
Loopholes.
Think you're smarter than me?
Then you can probably spell "TRAITOR"
Sure.
T-R-A-I-T-O-R. What
was the point of that?
Carol's keeping her fucking desk.
Good! She can have it.
I'm a field man now! Mowing
down vamps with my best friend Bud.
- That felt good.
- You did that.
Wait. Shit. What are you
gonna do about the money?
Oh, I'm good.
Think I'm gonna be all right.
And, uh...
fuck Carol.
Hey, should I drink Carol?
No, no, that's a lot of cholesterol.
Right, okay.
I won't go out of my way,
but if, like, there's a chance encounter
outside her house at night or...
- Yeah. Later.
- See you, guys!
- Bye.
- See you, guys.
What about us?
I was thinking,
what if we tried this whole, you know,
stay on the same groove type thing.
You know,
me cooking breakfast. You know?
How about we take it
one day at a time, but no more lies.
After what we've seen tonight,
there is no reason to lie.
So I ask you a question,
and you give me a straight answer.
I can live under those terms, you know.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't think we're there yet.
Mm-hmm. You just
gonna leave me like this?
Mmm. Jump back, want to kiss myself.
I'm gonna be
a vampire hunter too.
Uh...
- No.
- Daddy, why do you call me Pickle?
- Because that's what you are, baby.
Sometimes you're a sweet pickle,
sometimes you're a sour pickle,
and sometimes you're a salty pickle.
I love you, Daddy.
That's what I love about LA.
All the damn vampires.
♪ Every time I turn around
Every time they hear my sound ♪
♪ They get me all up underground
Still inside the box ♪
♪ Fuck what they say, just be
The Black folk like it, it's a hit ♪
♪ How can this true gangster shit
Be still outside the box? ♪
♪ We came from a place
Where our hearts are pure ♪
♪ People wanna know
What we're marchin' for ♪
♪ Grouped up, scooped up all my pals ♪
♪ Flavor for days, so much style
They can't even put it in a box now ♪
♪ Stepped out,
gator smile, wait a while ♪
♪ "Excuse me, Snoopy
Can we get a flick?" ♪
♪ I ain't really trippin',
Go on, take that shit ♪
♪ What? It's really gon'
be 'bout gettin' love ♪
♪ And that's only 'cause I give love ♪
♪ I stand up for it, I manned up for it
Like a brother 'posed to ♪
♪ Went through, go through
Goin' through, knowin' you ♪
♪ Showin' you, flowin' to
And the mental to grow into ♪
♪ Let bygones be bygones
So you can be an icon like I've done ♪
♪ Every time I turn around
Every time they hear my sound ♪
♪ They get me all up underground
Still inside the box ♪
♪ Own it like I want it, that's 24-7 ♪
♪ Me and my dawgs
On the highway to heaven ♪
♪ Just put a Funko in 7-11 ♪
♪ It's a trifecta
Me, Jasmine, and Kevin ♪
♪ Built a massive team
That's passion themed ♪
♪ Do it for the love
On top there's the cream ♪
♪ I do it 'til I did that, get enough ♪
♪ Run it up, rake enough
Make enough to give back ♪
♪ What? It's really gon'
be 'bout gettin' love ♪
♪ And that's only 'cause I give love ♪
♪ I stand up for it, I manned up for it
Still outside the box ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Best friend Bud
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Bud, Bud, Bud, Bud, Bud, Bud, Bud ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Hey, I think I just missed my flight
Privé Revaux to see through the lights ♪
♪ I'mma need some Advil and Pedialyte ♪
♪ 'Cause we've been on champagne
All damn night ♪
♪ Whoo! It's a masquerade
Came 30 deep in the Escalade ♪
♪ Then I told her
She better bring her friends ♪
♪ I'm stuck in the middle
Like Malcolm again ♪
♪ Whoo! That's my best friend
Whoo! No wedding ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ But if I did
Then Bud would have to be my best man ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Mowing down vamps
With my best friend Bud ♪
♪ Hit me ♪